If you want to live, you will obey.
Eagle Eye is a mystery, thriller, action film directed by D.J. Caruso.
Jerry Shaw and Rachel Holloman are two strangers whose lives are suddenly
thrown into turmoil by a mysterious woman they have never met.
Threatening their lives and family, the unseen caller uses everyday technology
to control their actions and push them into increasing danger.
As events escalate, Jerry and Rachel become the country's most-wanted
fugitives and must figure out what is happening to them.
Jerry Shaw, played by Shia LaBeouf.
Rachel Holloman, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Zoe Perez, played by Rosario Dawson.
Defense Secretary Callister, played by Michael Chiklis.
William Bowman, played by Anthony Mackie.
Toby Grant, played by Ethan Embry.
Eagle Eye is a 2008 American action thriller film directed by D.
Caruso from a screenplay by John Glenn, Travis Adam
Wright, Hillary Seitz and Dan McDermott.
The film stars Shia LaBeouf, Michelle Monaghan, Rosario Dawson,
Michael Chiklis, Anthony Mackie, and Billy Bob Thornton.
Its plot follows two strangers who are forced to go on the run together after receiving a mysterious phone call
from an unknown woman who uses information and communications technology to track their every move.
Eagle Eye was released in the United States on September 26, 2008.
Despite receiving mixed-to-negative reviews from critics, the film grossed
$178.8 million worldwide against an $80 million production budget.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence (a.i.),
washington dc, usa, technology, hostage, secret identity.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.